<resources>
    <string name="app_name">What_Movie_is_It_</string>
    <string name="which_movie_is_it">Which Movie is It?</string>
    <string name="buttonNext">Next</string>
    <string name="your_score">Your Score:</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer</string>
    <string name="noneRadioSelected">Choose a option</string>
    <string name="correctAnswer">Correct</string>
    <string name="incorrectAnswer">Incorrect</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">Read the synopsis and try to guess which movie it is</string>
    <string name="appName">Which movie is it?</string>
    <string name="startQuiz">Start</string>
    <string name="answerButton">Answer</string>
    <string name="nextButton">Next</string>
    <string name="resultScore">You scored:</string>
    <string name="buttonPlayAgain">Play Again</string>
    <string name="correctAnswers">Correct Answers:</string>
    <string name="question1">Two imprisoned men bond over a number of years, finding solace and eventual redemption through acts of common decency.</string>
    <string name="question2">The aging patriarch of an organized crime dynasty transfers control of his clandestine empire to his reluctant son.</string>
    <string name="question3">Two strangers, who awaken in a room with no recollection of how they got there, soon discover they\'re pawns in a deadly game perpetrated by a notorious serial killer.</string>
    <string name="question4">The lives of two mob hitmen, a boxer, a gangster and his wife, and a pair of diner bandits intertwine in four tales of violence and redemption.</string>
    <string name="question5">A thief who steals corporate secrets through the use of dream-sharing technology is given the inverse task of planting an idea into the mind of a C.E.O.</string>
    <string name="question6">A computer hacker learns from mysterious rebels about the true nature of his reality and his role in the war against its controllers.</string>
    <string name="question7">In Gotham City, mentally troubled comedian Arthur Fleck is disregarded and mistreated by society. He then embarks on a downward spiral of revolution and bloody crime. This path brings him face-to-face with his alter-ego.</string>
    <string name="question8">A family heads to an isolated hotel for the winter where a sinister presence influences the father into violence, while his psychic son sees horrific forebodings from both past and future.</string>
    <string name="question9">A pragmatic paleontologist visiting an almost complete theme park is tasked with protecting a couple of kids after a power failure causes the park\'s cloned dinosaurs to run loose.</string>
    <string name="question10">In a post-apocalyptic wasteland, a woman rebels against a tyrannical ruler in search for her homeland with the aid of a group of female prisoners, a psychotic worshiper, and a drifter named Max.</string>
    <string name="question11">A frontiersman on a fur trading expedition in the 1820s fights for survival after being mauled by a bear and left for dead by members of his own hunting team.</string>
    <string name="question12">A former Roman General sets out to exact vengeance against the corrupt emperor who murdered his family and sent him into slavery.</string>
    <string name="question13">After a space merchant vessel receives an unknown transmission as a distress call, one of the crew is attacked by a mysterious life form and they soon realize that its life cycle has merely begun.</string>
    <string name="question14">A cowboy doll is profoundly threatened and jealous when a new spaceman figure supplants him as top toy in a boy\'s room.</string>
    <string name="saw">Saw</string>
    <string name="godFather">The GodFather</string>
    <string name="matrix">Matrix</string>
    <string name="faceOff">Face-Off</string>
    <string name="shawShank">The Shawshank Redemption</string>
    <string name="bastards">Inglourious Basterds</string>
    <string name="alien">Alien</string>
    <string name="amadeus">Amadeus</string>
    <string name="darkKnight">BatMan: The Dark Knight</string>
    <string name="shining">The Shining</string>
    <string name="lambs">The silence of the lambs</string>
    <string name="joker">Joker</string>
    <string name="jurassic">Jurassic Park</string>
    <string name="inception">Inception</string>
    <string name="mad">Mad Max - Fury Road</string>
    <string name="renevant">The Renevant</string>
    <string name="toy">Toy Story</string>
    <string name="footLoose">FootLoose</string>
    <string name="pulp">Pulp Fiction</string>
    <string name="gladiator">Gladiator</string>

</resources>